# static question to store into csv file
academic_questions = [
    {"question": "What classes do I need to take for my major?",
     "answer": "You can find the required courses for your major in the university catalog or by scheduling a meeting "
               "with your academic advisor. They will guide you through the curriculum and help you plan your "
               "academic path."},
    {"question": "How do I register for classes?",
     "answer": "To register for classes, log in to the university portal, navigate to the 'Registration' section, "
               "and use the tools to search for and add courses. Consult your academic advisor beforehand to plan "
               "your schedule, and be mindful of prerequisites and registration timelines. If you encounter any "
               "issues, reach out to the registrar's office or your advisor for assistance."},
    {"question": "Can I change my major?",
     "answer": "Yes, you can change your major if you decide to pursue a different academic path. To do so, "
               "schedule a meeting with your academic advisor to discuss your interests and explore available "
               "options. They will guide you through the process, explain any implications on your coursework, "
               "and help ensure a smooth transition to your new major."},
    {"question": "What is the grading system here?",
     "answer": "Our university typically uses a letter grading system. A is for excellent, B for good, "
               "C for satisfactory, D for passing but below average, and F for failing. The grading scale may include "
               "plus and minus modifiers. You can find specific details in the university handbook or syllabus for "
               "each course."},
    {"question": "How do I find my class schedule",
     "answer": "To find your class schedule, log in to the university's online portal or student information system. "
               "Navigate to the 'Schedule' or 'Student Services' section, where you can view and access your detailed "
               "class schedule, including course names, times, and locations. If you encounter any difficulties, "
               "consult the university's guide or contact the registrar's office for assistance."},
    {"question": "How do I find my class schedule",
     "answer": "To find your class schedule, log in to the university's online portal or student information system. "
               "Navigate to the 'Schedule' or 'Student Services' section, where you can view and access your detailed "
               "class schedule, including course names, times, and locations. If you encounter any difficulties, "
               "consult the university's guide or contact the registrar's office for assistance."},
    {"question": "Are there tutoring services available",
     "answer": "Yes, tutoring services are available to assist you. The university provides resources through the "
               "Academic Support Center where you can schedule one-on-one sessions with tutors or participate in "
               "group study sessions. Check the center's schedule and offerings to access support tailored to your "
               "academic needs."},
    {"question": "How do I access the online learning platform?",
     "answer": "To access the online learning platform, log in to the university's website and navigate to the "
               "designated section for online courses or e-learning. There, you'll find a link or portal to the "
               "online learning platform. Use your university credentials to log in, and from the platform, "
               "you can access your courses, assignments, and other relevant materials. If you encounter any issues, "
               "reach out to the university's IT support for assistance."},
    {"question": "What is the policy on attendance?",
     "answer": "The university generally has an attendance policy that varies by course and instructor. It's crucial "
               "to review the syllabus for each class as it typically outlines the attendance expectations, "
               "including any penalties for excessive absences. Some professors may factor attendance into grading, "
               "while others may have specific requirements for participation. If you have concerns or need "
               "clarification, don't hesitate to discuss attendance policies with your instructors or refer to the "
               "university's academic policies outlined in the handbook."},
    {"question": "How can I add or drop a class?",
     "answer": "To add or drop a class, log in to the university's online portal or student information system. "
               "Navigate to the 'Registration' or 'Student Services' section and locate the option for adding or "
               "dropping classes. Follow the instructions provided, including selecting the course and confirming "
               "your changes. Be mindful of any deadlines, as there may be an add/drop period specified by the "
               "university. If you encounter difficulties or have questions, consult with your academic advisor or "
               "contact the registrar's office for guidance."},
    {"question": "Are there study groups for certain courses?",
     "answer": "Yes, there are often study groups available for certain courses. You can inquire about existing study "
               "groups through your professors, academic department, or student organizations related to your major. "
               "Additionally, the university's Academic Support Center may organize or facilitate study groups. "
               "Online platforms and bulletin boards on campus can also be sources for information about existing "
               "study groups, or you can consider forming one with classmates who share similar academic goals in "
               "your courses."},
]

campus_life_questions = [
    {"question": "Where is the student center located?",
     "answer": "The student center is typically located near the heart of the campus, often close to the main quad or "
               "central gathering area. Specific directions can be found on the campus map, available on the "
               "university's website or at information kiosks around campus. If you're unsure, feel free to ask "
               "fellow students, or seek assistance from campus staff or student guides who can direct you to the "
               "student center."},
    {"question": "What clubs and organizations can I join?",
     "answer": "There is a diverse range of clubs and organizations you can join based on your interests. Explore the "
               "university's club directory or attend a campus involvement fair to discover options. Common "
               "categories include academic clubs, cultural organizations, sports clubs, service groups, and special "
               "interest societies. Check the university's website or student affairs office for an updated list of "
               "active clubs and their meeting times. Feel free to attend introductory meetings to find the ones that "
               "align with your passions and goals."},
    {"question": "Are there on-campus jobs available for students?",
     "answer": "There is a diverse range of clubs and organizations you can join based on your interests. Explore the "
               "university's club directory or attend a campus involvement fair to discover options. Common "
               "categories include academic clubs, cultural organizations, sports clubs, service groups, and special "
               "interest societies. Check the university's website or student affairs office for an updated list of "
               "active clubs and their meeting times. Feel free to attend introductory meetings to find the ones that "
               "align with your passions and goals."},
    {"question": "How do I get involved in sports or intramurals?",
     "answer": "To get involved in sports or intramurals, visit the university's athletics department or recreation "
               "center. They typically have information on the sports offered, tryouts, and intramural schedules. "
               "Attend sports events to learn more about the teams and meet coaches. For intramurals, sign up for "
               "leagues or tournaments based on your interests and skill level. Keep an eye out for announcements or "
               "join sports-related clubs and organizations to stay informed about opportunities to participate and "
               "engage in the athletic community on campus."},
    {"question": "Where is the library, and what resources does it offer?",
     "answer": "The library is usually centrally located on campus. You can find its exact location on the campus map "
               "or by asking for directions at the information desk. The library offers a variety of resources, "
               "including an extensive collection of books, academic journals, and multimedia materials. "
               "Additionally, there are study spaces, computer labs, and often specialized services such as research "
               "assistance and tutoring. Visit the library's website or ask the librarians for guidance on accessing "
               "specific resources and utilizing the available services."},
    {"question": "What are the dining options on campus?",
     "answer": "On campus, you'll find a range of dining options catering to various preferences. There's typically a "
               "main cafeteria offering diverse meal choices, a coffee shop for quick bites and beverages, "
               "and a food court with different cuisines. Many universities also have dining halls that feature a "
               "variety of meal plans to choose from, allowing flexibility in your dining options. You can use your "
               "meal plan or dining dollars at these locations. Check the university's dining services website for "
               "menus, hours of operation, and details about the available meal plans."},
    {"question": "How can I get a student ID card?",
     "answer": "Visit the campus ID card office: Locate the campus ID card office, often found in the student center "
               "or a designated administrative building.Bring required documentation: Typically, you'll need to "
               "provide proof of enrollment, such as a class schedule or a registration confirmation, along with a "
               "government-issued photo ID."},
    {"question": "What are the fitness and recreation facilities on campus?",
     "answer": "On-campus, you'll find a variety of fitness and recreation facilities tailored to promote "
               "a healthy lifestyle. These may include well-equipped gyms, sports courts, swimming pools, and spaces "
               "for fitness classes and intramural sports. Check with your university's recreation department for "
               "specific details and opportunities to stay active and engaged on campus."},
    {"question": "Are there cultural events or activities on campus?",
     "answer": "Yes, campuses often host a vibrant array of cultural events and activities. These may include "
               "cultural festivals, art exhibitions, performances, and lectures featuring guest speakers. Check the "
               "university's events calendar or cultural affairs office for information on upcoming events that "
               "celebrate diversity, heritage, and the arts. Participating in these activities is a great way to "
               "engage with different cultures and broaden your perspectives."},
    {"question": "Can I bring a car to campus, and where can I park?",
     "answer": "Yes, many universities allow students to bring cars to campus. To find information on parking "
               "regulations and designated areas, visit the university's transportation or parking services website. "
               "There, you can learn about parking permits, rules, and any associated fees. Some universities have "
               "specific parking lots or garages for students, and it's important to familiarize yourself with the "
               "parking policies to ensure compliance and find convenient and secure parking for your vehicle."}
]

housing_questions = [
    {"question": "How do I apply for on-campus housing?",
     "answer": "To apply for on-campus housing, log in to the housing portal on the university's website using your "
               "student credentials. Fill out the housing application, indicating your preferences and any requested "
               "roommate information. Make sure to submit any required documents and pay associated fees as specified "
               "by the university. If you have questions, reach out to the housing office for assistance."},
    {"question": "Can I choose my roommate?",
     "answer": "Yes, many universities offer the option to choose your roommate during the on-campus housing "
               "application process. Typically, this involves mutual requests between you and a specific person. Make "
               "sure to coordinate with your preferred roommate and follow the guidelines provided by the university "
               "for submitting roommate requests. Keep in mind that roommate selection processes may vary between "
               "universities, so it's essential to check your university's specific housing policies and procedures."},
    {"question": "What items should I bring to my dorm?",
     "answer": "When packing for your dorm, bring essentials like bedding, towels, toiletries, school supplies, "
               "and personal items. Consider space limitations and check with your university for any specific "
               "recommendations or restrictions on appliances and furnishings."},
    {"question": "Are there laundry facilities available for students?",
     "answer": "Yes, the university provides laundry facilities for students. You can find these facilities in "
               "designated areas within or near the dormitories. Check the schedule and any associated fees or "
               "procedures for using the laundry services."},
    {"question": "How do I report maintenance issues in my dorm?",
     "answer": "To report maintenance issues in your dorm, contact the university's maintenance hotline or submit a "
               "work order through the online portal. Be specific about the issue, its location, and provide your "
               "contact information for follow-up."},
    {"question": "Can I have guests stay overnight in my dorm?",
     "answer": "Yes, most universities allow guests to stay overnight with prior approval from your roommate. Ensure "
               "your guest adheres to dorm policies, sign them in at the front desk, and communicate with your "
               "roommate to maintain a comfortable living environment."},
    {"question": " What are the rules for quiet hours in the dorms?",
     "answer": "Quiet hours in the dorms are typically established to ensure a conducive living environment for all "
               "residents. These hours, usually in the evenings, require reduced noise levels to promote a quiet "
               "study and sleep atmosphere. Check with your dormitory's guidelines for specific hours and "
               "expectations."},
    {"question": "Are there gender-neutral housing options?",
     "answer": "Yes, many universities offer gender-neutral housing options. This provides students with the choice "
               "to room with individuals regardless of gender. Check with the housing office to inquire about "
               "availability and the process for selecting gender-neutral housing"},
    {"question": "How safe is the campus and dormitory area?",
     "answer": "Campus safety is a top priority. Universities implement various security measures, including campus "
               "police, emergency call boxes, and surveillance. Research crime statistics, attend campus safety "
               "orientations, and utilize available resources to stay informed and contribute to a secure environment"},
    {"question": "What is the process for moving out at the end of the semester?",
     "answer": "At the end of the semester, you'll typically receive detailed instructions from the housing office "
               "regarding the move-out process. This may include specific checkout procedures, deadlines for vacating "
               "the dorm, and guidelines for returning keys or access cards. Be sure to follow these instructions to "
               "ensure a smooth move-out experience."},

]

financial_questions = [
    {"question": "How do I apply for financial aid?",
     "answer": "To apply for financial aid, complete the Free Application for Federal Student Aid (FAFSA) online. "
               "This form assesses your eligibility for grants, scholarships, and federal student loans. Check the "
               "university's financial aid office for additional application requirements and deadlines."},
    {"question": "When are tuition payments due?",
     "answer": "Tuition payment deadlines vary, and the university typically provides a schedule. Check with the "
               "bursar's office or the university's financial services website for specific due dates and information "
               "on payment methods, including any installment plans available"},
    {"question": "Are there scholarships available for freshmen?",
     "answer": "Yes, many universities offer scholarships specifically for incoming freshmen. Explore the "
               "university's scholarship portal, and consider checking with your academic department or the "
               "scholarship office for additional opportunities and application details."},
    {"question": "Can I work on campus to help cover expenses?",
     "answer": "Absolutely, you can work on campus to help cover expenses. Visit the university's career services or "
               "student employment office to explore available job opportunities. They can guide you through the "
               "application process and help you find suitable on-campus employment."},
    {"question": "What is the process for getting a student loan?",
     "answer": "To secure a student loan, start by completing the FAFSA to determine your eligibility for federal "
               "loans. Then, visit the university's financial aid office for guidance on the types of loans "
               "available, application procedures, and loan counseling. Be sure to understand the terms and repayment "
               "options before committing."},
    {"question": "Are there budgeting resources available for students?",
     "answer": "Yes, universities often provide budgeting resources to help students manage their finances. Visit the "
               "financial aid office or student services for workshops, online tools, and personalized advice on "
               "creating and maintaining a budget during your time at the university."},
    {"question": "How do I access my student account and billing information?",
     "answer": "Access your student account and billing information through the university's online portal. Log in "
               "with your student credentials, navigate to the 'Student Services' or 'Finances' section, and you'll "
               "find details on tuition, fees, and payment history."},
    {"question": "Are there discounts for local businesses with a student ID?",
     "answer": "Yes, many local businesses offer discounts to students with a valid university ID. Explore the "
               "university's website or ask at the student affairs office for a list of participating businesses and "
               "the specific discounts they offer."},
    {"question": "What is the cost of textbooks, and are there affordable options?",
     "answer": "Textbook costs vary, but universities often provide options for affordability. Consider purchasing "
               "used or digital textbooks, renting when possible, or exploring online platforms for discounted "
               "options. Check with the campus bookstore and the library for available resources and cost-saving "
               "strategies."}
]

resource_questions = [
    {"question": "How do I connect to the campus Wi-Fi?",
     "answer": "To connect to the campus Wi-Fi, locate the network named 'University Wi-Fi' in your device's "
               "settings. Enter your student credentials when prompted, and if you encounter any issues, "
               "the university's IT help desk is available for assistance."},
    {"question": "What technology resources are available for students?",
     "answer": "Students have access to various technology resources, including computer labs, software applications, "
               "and online platforms for coursework. Check with the university's IT department or visit the "
               "technology services website for a comprehensive list of available resources."},
    {"question": "Can I print documents on campus, and how much does it cost?",
     "answer": "Yes, you can print documents on campus at designated printing facilities. Printing costs vary, "
               "so check with the university's printing services for pricing details and available payment methods"},
    {"question": "Is there a tech support service for students?",
     "answer": "Absolutely, the university provides tech support services for students. Contact the IT help desk for "
               "assistance with issues related to campus Wi-Fi, software, hardware, or any other technology-related "
               "concerns."},
    {"question": "How do I access the university's online library resources?",
     "answer": "Accessing online library resources is typically done through the university's library website. Log in "
               "with your student credentials, and you can explore databases, journals, and other digital materials "
               "available for research and coursework."},
    {"question": "Are there computer labs available for student use?",
     "answer": "Yes, computer labs equipped with the latest software are available for student use across campus. "
               "Check the university's website or inquire at the library for information on lab locations, hours, "
               "and any specific guidelines for usage."},
    {"question": "Can I rent or borrow equipment like laptops or cameras?",
     "answer": "Many universities offer equipment rental services. Visit the library or technology services "
               "department to inquire about borrowing laptops, cameras, or other devices for academic purposes."},
    {"question": "How do I set up my university email account?",
     "answer": "Setting up your university email account is typically done through the university's IT portal or "
               "email services. Follow the instructions provided for account creation, and contact the IT help desk "
               "if you encounter any difficulties."},
    {"question": "What software is provided to students for free or at a discount?",
     "answer": "Students often have access to various software applications either for free or at a discounted rate. "
               "Visit the university's software services website or inquire with the IT department for a list of "
               "available software and licensing information."},
    {"question": "How do I log in to the online learning management system?",
     "answer": "To log in to the online learning management system, go to the university's e-learning platform and "
               "enter your student credentials. If you're facing issues, reach out to the IT support team or consult "
               "the provided user guides for assistance."}
]

health_questions = [
    {"question": "Where is the health center located?",
     "answer": "The health center is typically located on campus, and you can find its exact location on the "
               "university map or by asking at the information desk. Check the health services website for operating "
               "hours and any additional information."},
    {"question": "How do I schedule a medical appointment on campus?",
     "answer": "To schedule a medical appointment on campus, contact the health center either by phone or through the "
               "online patient portal. Provide your availability, and the staff will assist you in booking an "
               "appointment with a healthcare provider."},
    {"question": "Are there counseling services available for students?",
     "answer": "Yes, counseling services are available for students. You can schedule counseling appointments through "
               "the university's counseling center or mental health services. These services often include individual "
               "counseling, group therapy, and workshops."},
    {"question": "What health insurance options are available through the university?",
     "answer": "Universities typically offer health insurance plans for students. Visit the health services or "
               "student insurance office for information on available plans, coverage details, and the enrollment "
               "process"},
    {"question": "How can I maintain a healthy lifestyle on campus?",
     "answer": "Maintaining a healthy lifestyle on campus involves regular exercise, balanced nutrition, "
               "and sufficient rest. Take advantage of fitness facilities, explore wellness programs, and consider "
               "joining clubs or groups focused on health and well-being."},
    {"question": "Are there fitness classes or wellness programs?",
     "answer": "Yes, universities often offer fitness classes and wellness programs to promote a healthy campus "
               "community. Check the university's recreation or wellness center for information on available classes, "
               "workshops, and events."},
    {"question": "Where can I find information about vaccinations and immunizations?",
     "answer": "Information about vaccinations and immunizations can be obtained from the university health center or "
               "student health services. They can guide you on required vaccinations and provide details on available "
               "clinics or resources."},
    {"question": "What should I do in case of a medical emergency on campus?",
     "answer": "In case of a medical emergency on campus, call campus security or emergency services immediately. "
               "Familiarize yourself with the location of emergency response stations and always carry your "
               "identification and health insurance information."},
    {"question": "How do I access mental health resources?",
     "answer": "Accessing mental health resources is often done through the university's counseling or mental health "
               "services. Contact them to schedule appointments, attend workshops, or inquire about additional "
               "resources available to support your mental well-being."},
    {"question": "Are there recreational facilities like parks or trails nearby?",
     "answer": "Many campuses are situated near recreational facilities like parks or trails. Explore the local area "
               "or check with the university's recreation services for information on nearby outdoor spaces where you "
               "can engage in recreational activities and enjoy nature."}

]

internship_questions = [
    {"question": "How can I find internships related to my major?",
     "answer": "To find internships related to your major, utilize the university's career services office, "
               "online job boards, and networking events. Attend industry-specific events, connect with professors, "
               "and explore internship databases to discover relevant opportunities."},
    {"question": "Are there career counseling services available for students?",
     "answer": "Yes, most universities offer career counseling services. Schedule an appointment with the career "
               "center to receive guidance on career exploration, resume building, and job search strategies tailored "
               "to your goals and interests."},
    {"question": "When should I start thinking about my career after graduation?",
     "answer": "It's never too early to start thinking about your career after graduation. Begin exploring potential "
               "career paths during your freshman year, and consistently engage with career services to refine your "
               "goals and develop a strategic plan for post-graduation success."},
    {"question": "Is there a career fair or job expo on campus?",
     "answer": "Yes, many universities host career fairs or job expos. Attend these events to connect with employers, "
               "explore job opportunities, and network with professionals in your field. Check the university's event "
               "calendar or career services for details."},
    {"question": "Can I get help finding part-time or campus jobs?",
     "answer": "The university's career services office provides resources for resume building and interview "
               "preparation. Attend workshops, utilize online guides, and schedule mock interviews to enhance your "
               "skills and present yourself effectively to potential employers."},
    {"question": "How does the university support students in finding job opportunities?",
     "answer": "Absolutely, the university's career services or student employment office can assist you in finding "
               "part-time or on-campus jobs. Check job boards, attend job fairs, and consult with these offices for "
               "guidance on securing employment opportunities while studying."},
    {"question": "Are there networking events for students and alumni?",
     "answer": "Yes, universities often host networking events for students and alumni. Attend these events to expand "
               "your professional network, gain insights into different industries, and potentially discover "
               "mentorship opportunities"},
    {"question": "What companies or organizations typically recruit from this university?",
     "answer": "The university's career services office can provide information on companies and organizations that "
               "typically recruit from the institution. Attend career fairs, employer presentations, and networking "
               "events to connect with recruiters from these companies."},
    {"question": "How can I gain relevant experience in my field while in school?",
     "answer": "To gain relevant experience in your field while in school, explore internships, co-op programs, "
               "and volunteer opportunities. Connect with professors, join relevant student organizations, "
               "and seek out hands-on projects or research opportunities to enhance your skills and build a strong "
               "foundation for your future career."}
]

transport_questions = [
    {"question": "Is public transportation easily accessible from campus?",
     "answer": "Yes, public transportation is often easily accessible from campus. Check with the university's "
               "transportation services for information on local bus routes, train stations, or other public transit "
               "options available in the area."},
    {"question": "Can freshmen have cars on campus, and what are the parking regulations?",
     "answer": "Parking regulations for freshmen vary by university. Some may allow freshmen to have cars on campus "
               "with certain restrictions, while others may limit parking to upperclassmen. Review the university's "
               "parking policies for specific regulations and permit requirements."},
    {"question": "How do I navigate the campus shuttle system?",
     "answer": "To navigate the campus shuttle system, familiarize yourself with the shuttle routes and schedules "
               "provided by the university's transportation services. Shuttles often have designated stops at key "
               "locations on and around campus, making it convenient for students to travel between academic "
               "buildings and other destinations."},
    {"question": "Are there bike racks available on campus?",
     "answer": "Yes, most campuses have bike racks conveniently located throughout the campus. Use these racks to "
               "secure your bicycle while attending classes or exploring the campus. Check with the university's "
               "facilities or transportation services for the locations of bike racks."},
    {"question": "What are the transportation options for getting off-campus?",
     "answer": "For off-campus transportation, consider using public transit, rideshare services, or your personal "
               "vehicle if permitted. Additionally, universities may offer shuttle services or have designated "
               "pick-up locations for transportation services like buses and taxis."},
    {"question": "How far is the nearest airport, and are there shuttle services?",
     "answer": "The distance to the nearest airport varies by campus location. Check with the university's "
               "transportation services or airport shuttle information for details on available services. Some "
               "universities provide shuttle services to nearby airports for the convenience of students."}
]

social_life_questions = [
    {"question": "How can I make friends on campus?",
     "answer": "To make friends on campus, attend orientation events, join clubs or student organizations, "
               "and participate in social activities. Be open to meeting new people in your classes or residence "
               "hall, and don't hesitate to initiate conversations or attend campus social gatherings."},
    {"question": "What social events are planned for freshmen?",
     "answer": "Freshmen can expect a variety of social events planned by the university, including orientation "
               "activities, welcome receptions, and mixers. Check the university's event calendar or student affairs "
               "office for information on upcoming events specifically designed for freshmen."},
    {"question": "Are there fraternities or sororities on campus?",
     "answer": "Yes, many universities have fraternities and sororities. Explore Greek life on campus by attending "
               "rush events or informational meetings. Each organization typically hosts recruitment activities for "
               "students interested in joining."},
    {"question": "How can I get involved in the local community?",
     "answer": "To get involved in the local community, consider volunteering with local organizations, participating "
               "in community service events, or joining community-based clubs. Check with the university's community "
               "engagement or service-learning office for opportunities to connect with the local area."},
    {"question": "What are some popular hangout spots for students?",
     "answer": "Popular hangout spots for students often include cafes, student lounges, recreational areas, "
               "and campus green spaces. Explore the university's facilities, attend events, and ask upperclassmen "
               "for recommendations to discover the most popular spots for socializing."},
    {"question": "How do I join or create a student organization?",
     "answer": "To join a student organization, attend club fairs, browse the university's student organization "
               "directory, and connect with existing members. If you're interested in creating a new organization, "
               "contact the student affairs or student activities office for guidance on the process and "
               "requirements."},
    {"question": "Are there cultural or diversity events on campus?",
     "answer": "Yes, universities often host cultural and diversity events throughout the academic year. Attend "
               "cultural festivals, awareness weeks, and diversity celebrations organized by student groups, clubs, "
               "or the university's multicultural affairs office."},
    {"question": "What is the nightlife like around the university?",
     "answer": "The nightlife around the university varies based on location. Explore nearby bars, cafes, "
               "and entertainment venues to discover the local scene. Check for university-sponsored events, "
               "and ask fellow students for recommendations on popular nightlife spots in the area."},
]

international_student_questions = [
    {"question": "Are there resources for international students?",
     "answer": "Yes, universities provide a range of resources for international students. The international student "
               "services office offers assistance with visa processes, cultural adjustment, and general support to "
               "ensure a smooth transition to academic life."},
    {"question": "How do I navigate the visa and immigration process?",
     "answer": "Navigating the visa and immigration process is facilitated by the university's international student "
               "services. They offer guidance on visa application procedures, required documentation, and compliance "
               "with immigration regulations, ensuring a comprehensive understanding of the process."},
    {"question": "Are there cultural exchange programs or events?",
     "answer": "Many universities organize cultural exchange programs and events to foster a global community. Check "
               "with the international student services office and cultural affairs department for information on "
               "language exchange programs, international festivals, and cultural events."},
    {"question": "What support services are available for English language learners?",
     "answer": "Support services for English language learners are typically available through language centers or "
               "academic support services. The university may offer English as a Second Language (ESL) programs, "
               "tutoring, and language proficiency resources to help international students enhance their English "
               "skills."},
    {"question": "How can I connect with other international students?",
     "answer": "Connecting with other international students is facilitated through orientation programs, "
               "cultural events, and international student clubs. Attend social gatherings, join international "
               "student organizations, and participate in activities organized by the university to build a network "
               "within the international student community."},
    {"question": "Are there opportunities to study abroad during my time here?",
     "answer": "Yes, many universities offer study abroad programs allowing students to explore academic "
               "opportunities in other countries. Connect with the university's study abroad office to learn about "
               "available programs, application processes, and the criteria for participating in these enriching "
               "experiences."}
]

other_questions = [
    {"question": "What is the policy on academic integrity and plagiarism?",
     "answer": "The university upholds strict policies on academic integrity and plagiarism. Familiarize yourself "
               "with the university's code of conduct, attend any required workshops, and ensure you understand the "
               "guidelines for proper citation and academic honesty"},
    {"question": "How do I contact my professors outside of class?",
     "answer": "Professors can typically be contacted through email or during their office hours. Check the course "
               "syllabus for contact information, and consider sending a concise and polite email if you have "
               "questions or need additional clarification outside of class."},
    {"question": "What should I do if I miss a class due to illness?",
     "answer": "If you miss a class due to illness, inform your professors as soon as possible. Check the syllabus "
               "for specific instructions on makeup work or missed assignments and consider reaching out to "
               "classmates for any notes or materials you may have missed."},
    {"question": "How can I access disability services if needed?",
     "answer": "For disability services, contact the university's disability resource center. They can provide "
               "information on available accommodations, support services, and the process for registering with the "
               "center to ensure your needs are addressed"},
    {"question": "Are there opportunities for undergraduate research?",
     "answer": "Yes, many universities offer opportunities for undergraduate research. Explore research centers, "
               "connect with faculty members in your field of interest, and inquire about research assistant "
               "positions or projects to get involved in hands-on academic experiences."},
    {"question": "Can I bring a pet to campus?",
     "answer": "Check the university's pet policy, as rules regarding pets on campus vary. Some universities have "
               "designated pet-friendly housing or allow pets in specified areas. Familiarize yourself with the "
               "guidelines and register your pet accordingly if permitted."},
    {"question": "How do I sign up for campus tours or orientations?",
     "answer": "To sign up for campus tours or orientations, visit the university's admissions or orientation "
               "website. Many universities provide online registration forms or contact information for scheduling "
               "guided tours and orientation sessions to help you become familiar with the campus."},
    {"question": "What is the policy on student conduct and disciplinary actions?",
     "answer": "Review the university's student handbook or code of conduct for information on student conduct "
               "policies and disciplinary actions. Understand the expectations, follow campus rules, "
               "and seek guidance from the student affairs office if you have questions or concerns."},
    {"question": "How do I report concerns about campus safety or security?",
     "answer": "Report concerns about campus safety or security to the university's campus police or security office. "
               "They can provide guidance on emergency procedures and address any safety-related issues you may "
               "observe on campus."},
    {"question": "Can I request a change in my class schedule?",
     "answer": "Yes, you can often request a change in your class schedule during the designated add/drop period. "
               "Consult the university's registrar's office or student services for information on the process, "
               "deadlines, and any considerations regarding your academic program."},
    {"question": "What advice do you have for success as a freshman at this university?",
     "answer": "My advice for success as a freshman is to attend orientation events, get involved in campus "
               "activities, manage your time effectively, and seek support when needed. Utilize resources such as "
               "tutoring, counseling services, and faculty office hours to maximize your academic and personal growth "
               "during your time at the university."},
    {"question": "What is enrolment?",
     "answer": "Induction is a process where you are introduced to your course, university, and other "
               "students. It usually takes place in the first few days of starting university."},
    {"question": "What is induction?",
     "answer": "Induction is a process where you are introduced to your course, university, and other students. It "
               "usually takes place in the first few days of starting university."},
    {"question": "What is a personal tutor?",
     "answer": "A personal tutor is a member of academic staff who provides academic support and guidance throughout "
               "your course."},
    {"question": "How do I contact my personal tutor?",
     "answer": "You can contact your personal tutor through your university's student support services or by email."},
    {"question": "What is a lecture?",
     "answer": "A lecture is a type of teaching session where a lecturer delivers a presentation on a specific topic."},
    {"question": "What is a seminar?",
     "answer": "A seminar is a type of teaching session where students discuss and debate a specific topic in a small "
               "group."},
    {"question": "What is a tutorial?",
     "answer": "A tutorial is a type of teaching session where a tutor provides one-to-one or small group support and "
               "guidance on a specific topic."},
    {"question": "What is a student ID card?",
     "answer": "A student ID card is a form of identification that shows you are a student at your university."},
    {"question": "What is Freshers Week?",
     "answer": "Freshers Week is a week-long programme of social events, activities, and induction sessions for new "
               "students."},
    {"question": "What is a Freshers Fair?",
     "answer": "A Freshers Fair is an event where clubs, societies, and local businesses promote their services and "
               "products to new students."},
    {"question": "What is student accommodation like?",
     "answer": "Student accommodation can vary, but usually involves living in shared accommodation such as halls of "
               "residence or a shared house. The UniGuide has a useful guide on "
               "https://www.theuniguide.co.uk/advice/student-accommodation "},
    {"question": "What are the different types of student accommodation?",
     "answer": "The different types of student accommodation include halls of residence, shared houses, "
               "private rented accommodation, and student apartments. Types of student accommodation depend on where "
               "you are, your budget and your university."},
    {"question": "What is the cost of student accommodation?",
     "answer": "The cost of student accommodation varies depending on the type of accommodation and location. Check "
               "with your university for the specific costs."},
    {"question": "How do I apply for student accommodation?",
     "answer": "You can apply for student accommodation through your university's accommodation office. The "
               "application process varies depending on the specific accommodation."},
    {"question": "What is a tenancy agreement?",
     "answer": "A tenancy agreement is a legal document that sets out the terms and conditions of renting a property."},
    {"question": "What should I look for in a tenancy agreement?",
     "answer": "When looking for a tenancy agreement, you should check the terms and conditions of the agreement, "
               "including rent, deposit, and length of tenancy. The Citizens Advice website has a guide on "
               "https://www.citizensadvice.org.uk/housing/renting-a-home/"},
    {"question": "What is a deposit for student accommodation?",
     "answer": "A deposit for student accommodation is a sum of money paid to the landlord or accommodation provider "
               "to cover any damage or unpaid rent at the end of the tenancy."},
    {"question": "How do I get my deposit back for student accommodation?",
     "answer": "To get your deposit back for student accommodation, you should leave the accommodation in good "
               "condition and pay any outstanding rent. The landlord or accommodation provider will then return the "
               "deposit, minus any deductions."},
    {"question": "How do I get my deposit back for student accommodation?",
     "answer": "To get your deposit back for student accommodation, you should leave the accommodation in good "
               "condition and pay any outstanding rent. The landlord or accommodation provider will then return the "
               "deposit, minus any deductions."},
    {"question": "How do I register with a doctor at university?",
     "answer": "You can register with a doctor at university by contacting the health centre or medical practice on "
               "campus. They often have guides on which local doctors practices to register with, and how to go about "
               "that process."},
    {"question": "How much does university cost?",
     "answer": "The cost of university varies depending on the course and university. Check with your university for "
               "the specific fees."},
    {"question": "How do I pay for university?",
     "answer": "You can pay for university through student loans, bursaries, and scholarships. The Student Finance "
               "website covers how to pay for university."},
    {"question": "What is a student loan?",
     "answer": "A student loan is a type of loan that helps students pay for their tuition fees and living costs."},
    {"question": "How do I apply for a student loan?",
     "answer": "You can apply for a student loan through the Student Finance website. The application process varies "
               "depending on the specific loan."},
    {"question": "What is a student bursary?",
     "answer": "A student bursary is a form of financial support that does not have to be repaid."},
    {"question": "How do I apply for a student bursary?",
     "answer": "You can apply for a student bursary through your university or through external organisations. Check "
               "with your university for the specific application process."},
    {"question": "What is a student bank account?",
     "answer": "A student bank account is a bank account designed for students, with features like interest-free "
               "overdrafts and low fees."},
    {"question": "How do I open a student bank account?",
     "answer": "You can open a student bank account by contacting a bank or building society that offers student "
               "accounts. Money Saving Expert has a handy list of student bank accounts."},
    {"question": "How do I open a student bank account?",
     "answer": "You can open a student bank account by contacting a bank or building society that offers student "
               "accounts. Money Saving Expert has a handy list of student bank accounts."},
    {"question": "How do I avoid plagiarism?",
     "answer": "You can avoid plagiarism by properly citing and referencing any sources you use in your work."},
    {"question": "How do I reference my work?",
     "answer": "You can reference your work using a specific referencing style, such as Harvard or APA. Your "
               "university or course may have specific referencing guidelines."},
    {"question": "How do I use the library?",
     "answer": "You can use the library by checking out books and other resources, using study spaces, and accessing "
               "online resources. Check with your university for specific library services."},
    {"question": "What is a careers service?",
     "answer": "A careers service is a support service that provides advice and guidance on career planning, "
               "job searching, and employability."},
    {"question": "What is a graduate scheme?",
     "answer": "A graduate scheme is a structured training programme for recent graduates, usually provided by large "
               "employers."},
    {"question": "How do I find a graduate scheme?",
     "answer": "You can find a graduate scheme by checking job boards, networking, and contacting potential employers."},
    {"question": "What is a job fair?",
     "answer": "A job fair, or careers fair, is an event where employers and job seekers can connect and network."},
    {"question": "What is networking?",
     "answer": "Networking is the process of making professional connections and building relationships in a specific "
               "industry or field."}
]

categories = ["Academic & Lectures", "Campus Life & Networking", "Accommodation & Housing",
              "Resources and Library", "Health", "Internship and Volunteering",
              "Transportation", "Social life", "For international students", "Others"]

data = [
    {"category": "Academic & Lectures",
     "questions": academic_questions},
    {"category": "Campus Life & Networking",
     "questions": campus_life_questions},
    {"category": "Accommodation & Housing",
     "questions": housing_questions},
    {"category": "Resources and Library",
     "questions": resource_questions},
    {"category": "Health",
     "questions": health_questions},
    {"category": "Internship and Volunteering",
     "questions": internship_questions},
    {"category": "Transportation",
     "questions": transport_questions},
    {"category": "Social life",
     "questions": social_life_questions},
    {"category": "For international students",
     "questions": international_student_questions},
    {"category": "Others",
     "questions": other_questions}
]
